FARAZ KORASANI

Sydney NSW 2067 0451 287 563

faraz.korasani@gmail.com

Published Australian educator, administration officer, and technical artist and writer with 20 years of experience

Video editing, creative coding, and multimedia design sample portfolio: https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLeWo_gBNntCwpofiHMAmptDWXtFw40SES&si=4I2rS96wzYZ5rU01

Personal GitHub Website: https://farazkorasani.github.io/portfolio/

4 years as the Chief Administration Officer at Dr. Rafi's Educational Centre
5 years as the lead Pathway Teacher for university-bound students at ILSC Sydney, Australia's largest English school
Master's in English literature, Bachelor's in computer science

Skills

- Office Administration (scheduling, record-keeping, and reporting)
- Document Management (data entry, proofreading, and editing)
- Customer Service (liaising with clients and stakeholders)
- Technology Proficiency (MS Office Suite, database management)
- Video Editing (FlexClip)
- Graphic Design (Adobe Photoshop, Figma)
- Web Design (HTML, CSS)
- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Creative Coding (Processing, P5.js)
- Creative Writing (essays, reviews, blogs, etc)
- Game Development (Unity, C#)

Qualifications

- Cambridge CELTA (pass B) International House Sydney, Sydney, Australia
- Master's Degree in English Literature
- Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science
- Academic IELTS 8.5
- General IELTS 8.5
- iBT (TOEFL) 118
- GRE 320 (Full Verbal Score)

Publications

• Faraz Korasani. "Q Skills for Success Level 2 Book Review". *English Australia Journal* 37.1 (2021): 103-107.

Professional Experience

Dr. Haleh Rafi's Educational Centre - Melbourne, Australia

Chief Administration Officer, Aug 2020 – Present

- Coordinate administrative operations, including scheduling, student record maintenance, and correspondence
- Designed and implemented workflows to improve office efficiency and client satisfaction

PrepBox China - Sydney, Australia

Online ELA English Teacher, Jun 2024 – Present

- Exam prep (TOEFL, IELTS)
- Academic/Creative Writing

ILSC Sydney - Sydney, Australia

English Teacher, Mar. 2019 - Apr. 2024

- IELTS Preparation Courses (Online and On-Campus)
- English for Academic Purposes Courses (Online and On-Campus)

International House Sydney- Sydney, Australia

English Teacher, Jan. 2019 – Feb. 2019

• General English courses; English File 3rd Edition

References

- Dr. Haleh Rafi; Senior Research Development Coordinator at Monash University, Melbourne, Australia; haleh.rafi1@monash.edu
- Aaron Clark; Head Teacher at ILSC Australia; Aaron.Clark@ilsc.com.au